And we also have the option to create images with Gemini.
So I click on new chat and this time I ask Gemini to help me with, let's say,
"Hey, Gemini, I want to have an image of an elephant suited up."
And saying a polite, saying a joke, let's say.
Politely, I want the elephant to look as elite and as wise as possible.
And I open these tools and I click create images.
So by clicking submit, I will be able to wait until my images created.
So, as you see, it says loading nano-banana.
Nano-banana is the tool that Gemini uses for image creation.
It's also owned by Gemini, you know.
It's actually Gemini.
Here's an image of an elephant in a suit ready to share a joke.
Yes, so as you see, this is my elephant.
So he says, "Why don't elephants use computers?"
They're afraid of them.
So, it's not even funny, bro.
Yes, this is what we got, the elephant suited up telling us an elite joke and other animals
are seated around.
As you see, I love the lion over there.
Whatever.
So, this is also what we got with image creation with Gemini.